Nazarii Karpa

Frontend Developer

Phone number

E-mail

+380680553174

manbet2004@gmail.com

Portfolio

https://karpanazarii.github.io/Nazarii.Karpa.Portfolio2022/

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/nazariikarpa/

Address

Profile

Lviv, Ukraine



I want to find a progressive team and develop as a Front End programmer. I have the opportunity to work remotely in safe and comfortable conditions, and I can also work in the office. I already have experience and knowledge in the field of the front end. I have pet projects and certificates that you can see in my portfolio.

Experience

Artelogic

01.09.2022 - 01.11.2022

Trainee Web Developer Remote

I was qualified as a Trainee at Artelogic and enrolled in Web Development Internship.

Technologies:

HTML, CSS, SCSS/SASS, Less, Gulp, JavaScript

Trainee WebUI Developer(Intership) Remote

SoftServe

01.03.2022 - 01.04.2022

Passed Technical testing (Web UI 775.51/1000) and English language test (A2-B2+ / 65.31/100.00).

Successfully passed the interview in English and was involved in the WebUI club, but this club was canceled due to the war.

Education

Web Developer courses

08.04.2022 - 10.02.2023

ITVDN

HTML coder courses

04.07.2021 - 04.01.2022

HTML Academy

HTML coder marathon

01.06.2021 - 20.01.2021

GoIT

Languages

Ukrainian(Native)

English (B2)

Certification

Angular Essential

TestProvider Certificate of achievement Dmytro Okhrimenko (Chief Executive Officer, TestProvider), Igor Lisitsky (Head of UCC)

10.02.2023 - ∞

Registration number: TP15785432; This document acknowledges that: **Nazarii Karpa**. Has successfully passed the test HTML5&CSS3 (Score: 800/1000)

React Essential

TestProvider Certificate of achievement Dmytro Okhrimenko (Chief Executive Officer, TestProvider), Igor Lisitsky (Head of UCC)

19.07.2022 - ∞

Registration number: TP34435789; This document acknowledges that: **Nazarii Karpa**. Has successfully passed the test React Essential (Score: 880/1000)

HTML5 & CSS3

TestProvider Certificate of achievement Dmytro Okhrimenko (Chief Executive Officer, TestProvider), Igor Lisitsky (Head of UCC)

 $21.04.2022 - \infty$

Registration number: TP72627379; This document acknowledges that: **Nazarii Karpa**. Has successfully passed the test HTML5&CSS3 (Score: 886/1000)

JavaScript

TestProvider Certificate of achievement Dmytro Okhrimenko (Chief Executive Officer, TestProvider), Igor Lisitsky (Head of UCC)

08.04.2022 - ∞

Registration number: TP30195337; This document acknowledges that: **Nazarii Karpa**. Has successfully passed the test JavaScript Starter (Score: 829/1000)

English HTML

GolT, Anton Chorny

01.06.2021 - 20.06.2021

Has successfully completed training "GoIT English HTML"